This is the Master Resume. It contains all of my experience, projects, skills, etc. in a copy-and-pastable format for use in resume templates and finished resumes.

To use: cherry-pick each project and description bullets, then combine/reword list items as needed to fit the role's description perfectly.

#### Skills Covered:

- React
- TypeScript
- JavaScript
- Frontend Frameworks
- Git
- Responsive design
- Mobile Development
- UI Design
- Figma
- Adobe Creative Suite
- Tailwind
- Communication / Collaboration
- REST API
- Data visualization
- Development life cycle
- CI/CD
- React Native
- Google Cloud
- OAuth
- Node.js
- Express
- Retail Experience
- Asynchronous programming
- JIRA

#### Skills Missing:

- HTML/CSS & Styling
  - o HTML/CSS
- UI/UX Design
  - o UI Design Best Practices
  - Accessibility
  - Interaction Design
  - Motion Design
- Frontend Frameworks & Libraries
  - o Vue
  - o Angular
  - o Next.js

- o Redux
- o Context API
- o Storybook
- o Motion.dev
- Testing Frameworks & Tools
  - Cypress
  - Jest
- Build Tools & Package Managers
  - o Npm
  - o Yarn
  - Webpack
  - o Vite
- Content Management Systems (CMS)
  - o WordPress
  - o Contentful
  - o Builder.io
  - o Sitecore
  - o Shopify
  - o HubSpot
  - o HubL
- Backend Development
  - o Django
  - o Ruby on Rails
  - o Python
  - o Java
  - o Postgres
  - o SQL
  - o Multi-Tenant SaaS
- APIs & Data Formats
  - o GraphQL
  - o JSON
  - o XML
  - o Segment
- Optimization & SEO
  - o Optimization
  - o SEO
- Hosting & Cloud Services
  - o Vercel
  - o Netlify
  - o AWS
- DevOps & Build Pipelines
  - o Docker
  - Jenkins
  - o Build Pipelines

- o Bash / Command Line
- Project Management & Methodologies
  - o Remote Experience
  - Lead Projects
  - o Agile
- Problem Solving & Debugging
- Open Source Contributions
- Specialized Integration
  - Video Integration
  - o OMSDK
- Machine Learning

# **Professional Summary**

Include this when the role is in a small business or the job description puts particular stress on the personality characteristics of the applicant.

## Education

Optionally include relevant coursework

UNIVERSITY OF MARYLAND — Bachelor in Web and Digital Design

May 2023 - December 2024

•

**UNIVERSITY OF EDINBURGH** — Bachelor in International Business & Chinese September 2019 - November 2022

• Best Presenter Award 2020 by Dean of Business School for excellent communication

# Work Experience

**KOOLISOO STUDIOS Startup Co-Founder & Software Engineer** 

### April 2023 - Present

- Planned and implemented a gamified e-sports prediction website, attracting 854 users in one week
- Used Figma to design responsive UX/UI for all 7 web pages
- Implemented RESTful API using Express.js, using MongoDB for NoSQL database storage
- Integrated React frontend with Express backend REST API.
- Worked with asynchronous programming in TypeScript using Axios and Fetch API
- Deployed new versions using Google Firebase, with GitlabCI for creating CI/CD pipelines
- Integrated Google Analytics and deployed a cloud-based production environment with Google Cloud
- Integrated authorization using Discord OAuth and Supabase.

#### **ROVER STORE, INC**

#### **Software Engineer Contractor**

March 2024 - November 2024

- Designed and developed task automation UI using React, TypeScript, and Material UI, saving 11 hours of labor per week
- Collaborated with stakeholders to identify requirements for task automation UI
- Integrated Apache ECharts library for inventory & sales data visualization
- Used JIRA for workflow management and Git for version control

#### **MOGE TEE**

#### **Crew Member**

August 2021 - March 2023

- Increased kitchen preparation efficiency, improving prep time by 50%
- Trained and mentored over 10 new employees
- Interacted with hundreds of customers daily, solving problems and fulfilling customer requests
- Fixed POS system errors and ensured all aspects of day-to-day operations ran smoothly
- Worked with a team of 10-20 members in groups of 2-4 to serve thousands of customers
- Worked in a fast-paced, high-pressure environment
- Multitasked, overseeing both front-of-house and kitchen operations simultaneously

## **Projects**

### **DISCORD MUSIC BOT** | JavaScript, MongoDB, Express.js, Discord.js

- Implemented RESTful API using Express.js, integrating with MongoDB database
- Created commands and managed bot interactions using Discord.js and discord-player npm library

#### LIVE MUSICIAN MARKETPLACE APP | TypeScript, React Native

- Used React Native for iOS and Android application development
- Created wireframes & functional prototype using Figma

#### HABIT BUILDING APP | TypeScript, React, Google Cloud

- Designed UI components using Figma
- Implemented responsive UI using React and TypeScript

### POETRY FLOW APP | TypeScript, Svelte, TailwindCSS

• Designed UI using Figma

- Implemented responsive UI using Svelte, TypeScript, and TailwindCSS
- Wrote web scraping scripts in Python using Selenium and Beautiful Soup libraries

## Skills

Languages: TypeScript, JavaScript, HTML, CSS, Python, Java, PHP, SQL

Frameworks: React, Node.js, Express, Svelte

Tools: Figma, Adobe Creative Suite, Git, JIRA, Google Cloud, npm

Other: Mandarin, Romanian

# Wild Cards (bullet points to add to any project)

- Used Git for version control
- Used JIRA for workflow management